{
    "id": "6e2528e254154f9281be4ef061f2e40d",
    "title": "Wish",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9f35fd189a14420ead4b0eb1870d6734",
            "title": "Wish",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ……………… speak English.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you ………………… stop making that noise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. to the manager.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wish to talk",
                        "am wishing to talk",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish that I ………………… better looking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "am"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. your exams.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wish you would pass",
                        "hope you pass"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I …………………. there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ………………… that yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hadn't said",
                        "didn't say"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish you …………………. stop smoking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "could",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish today ………………… Sunday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "would be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wish I ………………… somewhere else.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "live",
                        "lived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}